# **Rud Stanislav**

Junior Front End developer



### Objective:

I want to change the direction of my life, start a career as a junior Front-end developer in company, and maybe in 5 years grow to the team leader.

#### Summary:

I have more than 3 years of experience with hosts on platforms: ESXI, Hyper-V, Proxmox, about 1.5 years of deployment of web servers on apache24, ngnix, ISS, and their support. Introduced jira CRM system to support users by developers. Launched corporate mail, ip-telephony. Physical servers of the company were transferred to virtual ones. Configured the monitoring system. Debugged the servers.

In my spare time I create one-page sites according to layouts. And I constantly improve my skills in site development.

I have an understanding and a small experience of working with assemblers Gulp, Webpack, Grunt.

Have experience with Photoshop.

#### > Skills:

- HTML5/CSS3 (Responsive, Adaptive)
- JavaScript
- Adobe Photoshop
- Version Control (Git)
- Virtualizations (VMware Workstation, Hiper-V, Proxmox, ESXI)
- Active network equipment (MikroTik, Ubiquiti, Fortigate, HP)
- Win servers
- Linux systems
- Web Servers (apache24, nginx, IIS)
- Database (MS SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL)
- CRM (Jira, Mantis, Bitrix24, 1C)

## Work Experience:

(2018 - today) System Administrator, GROUP OF COMPANIES «FACTOR»

- Server management, workstations, routers, switches and existing network applications.
- Monitoring and daily system checks.
- Diagnostics and solution of all technical problems related to hardware and software.
- Support for all network systems LAN, WAN.
- Ensuring network security and integrity.
- Backup, data recovery in case of failures or other situations, system and data recovery.

(2015 - 2018) System Administrator, Chain of supermarkets «CHUDO»

- Server management, workstations, computers, laptops, printers, routers, switches and existing network applications.
- Monitoring and daily system checks.
- Diagnose and solve all technical problems related to hardware and software.
- Laying, construction, support of all network systems LAN, WAN.
- Ensuring security and integrity of the network.
- Backup, data recovery in case of failures or other situations, system and data recovery.
- Opening of new branches, shops.
- Connecting and configuring commercial equipment.
- Remote user support.
- Working with users.
- Tenders and contracts with equipment suppliers.

#### **Education:**

KHAI - (2007 - 2011)

Bachelor - Engineer Constructor Aircrafts and Helicopters.

KHAI - (2011 - 2013)

Specialist - Aircraft Testing and Certification.

Telesens Academy – (2015)

QA Core (manual testing WEB, mobile, desktop, check-list, test-cases, bag-report)

NT School – Front-end developer (2018)

HTML5/CSS3/SCSS/Flex-box/Grid CSS.

In practice, I made one-page websites on PSD layouts and uploaded to hosting (no js, just HTML + CSS)

A-Level - Full Stack(2018-2019)

HTML5/CSS3/Flex-Box/JS/Git.

In practice, I made one-page websites on PSD layouts and uploaded to hosting.

# > Additional information:

I am currently working as a system administrator, but I really want to change my profession and start a career as a front-end developer. In my spare time I improve my skills in development, create one-page sites according to the layouts. Watching JS lessons, learning English.

- Quickly learning
- Fulfillment of tasks in good faith
- Initiative
- Executive
- Punctual
- Hard-working
- Responsible
- There is a great desire to learn new things and develop

Marital status: Married.

Hobby: I like to pick mushrooms, walk kayaks, ride bicycles, drive a car. .

Languages:

English pre-intermediate.